It's Friday! Enjoy Simple English! 森崎ウィンです
毎週金曜日は怪盗紳士ルパンの名作をお届けします
今日は遅すぎたシャーロックホームズの第3話です
画家ベルモに憤したルパン
お城から宝石類を盗んでいる最中
なんと以前愛した女性ネリに会います
どうなるんでしょうか
それではLet's dive into the story!
でフォアブラックフェイスドゥヴァン イントリュースミスネリーとヴェルモン
ミスネリーシーンでヴェルヴェス アイフォーガー
ユーメイト r 戦ルーパーアン ドゥスティンシュー
ビフォーエーサーレッシュ ソユーノーエスフェイス
ダーレスはユーエーションと c ヴェルモン
ヒーロースベリーセンブルーとルーパン
ダーゼンティー ミスネリーでノートレプライ
デヴァンのお客さんは 朝ごはんを頂き カーフィーに移動しました
ヌリーは 夜の前から ルポンの約束を忘れていませんでした
約束しました
明日の3時に 全てのメッセージが返されます
現在は3時20分です
ヌリーは 毎分10時から3時から5時まで 確認していました
時計が3回鳴ったと同時に
2台の荷物が出てきました
荷物と作品が売られていたのです
ネリー・サン・ヴェルモンは彼女に向かって歩きました
私は私の誓いを持っていました
ネリー・サン・ヴェルモンは静かに言っていました
私たちはステームシップで楽しい時間を過ごしたことを覚えていますか?
is it possible for you to forget about last night
miss nelly raised her eyes and pointed at a ruby ring on his finger
it was a ring that he had stolen from devon
he smiled sadly and said
you are right
nothing can be changed
our saint lupin will always be our saint lupin
forgive me
miss nelly walked past lupin
and disappeared into the castle.
I should leave before Sherlock Holmes arrives.
thought Lupin.
Lupin walked through a field to take a shortcut to the nearest train station.
There, he met someone traveling in the opposite direction.
It was a man about fifty years of age.
He was tall, looked like a foreigner, and carried a walking stick.
The man spoke to Lupin.
Excuse me, sir. Is this the way to the castle?
Yes, it is. They are waiting for you.
Oh?
My friend, Devon, told us last night that you were coming.
I am very happy to be the first person to welcome you, Sherlock Holmes.
There is no one who admires you more than me.
ルポンは彼の言葉の選択をすぐに悔しめました
ホームズは彼をとても近くに見つけました
ルポンは
彼は私を見せる必要があり、私はルポンだと知っていました
その時、戦士たちが乗り越え始めました
ルポンは
彼は戦士たちに呼びかけられ、私を捕まえますかと考えました
でもホームズは何も言いませんでした
It took a while for the last man to pass, and when he did, both men looked into each other's eyes.
It was an interesting sight.
The first meeting of two incredible men was so strange and so powerful.
The Englishman was the first to speak.
Thank you, sir.
You are quite welcome, replied Lupin.
and they went in different directions.
Lupon to the train station
and Sherlock Holmes to the castle.
来たー!ついにホームズ登場やっと来たよ!
もう待ったよ、ホームズ君!
てかもう、すごい二人の対面ですよ!
来週どうなっちゃうんでしょう?
Make sure to join us next Monday!